{
    "subject": "resource/The_Decalogue_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "Poland",
    "human_readable": "The Decalogue (TV series) is from Poland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854871034622192,
            "question": "Is 'The Decalogue' a Polish TV series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9017214179039001,
            "question": "Is 'The Decalogue' a Polish production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7833817005157471,
            "question": "Where is the TV series 'The Decalogue' from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6471886038780212,
            "question": "Which country is associated with the TV series 'The Decalogue'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5633405447006226,
            "question": "Can you tell me the origin of 'The Decalogue'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5631884336471558,
            "question": "What is the origin country of 'The Decalogue'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43871986865997314,
            "question": "What country produced 'The Decalogue'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4034792482852936,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the creators of 'The Decalogue'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3933055102825165,
            "question": "Is 'The Decalogue' a foreign production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3686612546443939,
            "question": "Where was 'The Decalogue' filmed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Decalogue (TV series) is from Poland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7090_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Decalogue' a foreign production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7090_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of the creators of 'The Decalogue'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7090_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country produced 'The Decalogue'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7090_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7090_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all five documents mention that \"The Decalogue\" was originally made for Polish television. This consistent information across multiple sources supports the triple being true."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"The Decalogue\" is a Polish television series, thus confirming the statement \"The Decalogue (TV series) is from Poland.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}